output.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy - Output

At Output, we deeply care about your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors and service users especially when it comes to personal information. This policy explains our privacy practices and applies where we are acting as a data controller with respect to the personal data of our website visitors and service users.

#### 1\. Introduction

1.1 By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

1.2 Our website incorporates privacy controls which affect how we will process your personal data. By using the privacy controls, you can specify whether you would like to receive direct marketing communications and limit the use of your information. You can access the privacy controls via the account section at Output.com

1.3 In this policy, “we”, “us” and “our” refer to Output. For more information about us, see Section 11.

#### 2\. How we use your personal data

2.1 We may process data about your use of our website and services (“usage data”). The usage data may include your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. The source of the usage data is Google Analytics, Amplitude, and Zaius. This usage data may be processed for the purposes of analyzing the use of the website and services. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely monitoring and improving our website and services.

2.2 We may process your account data (“account data”). The account data may include your name, email address, billing address, and shipping address. The source of the account data is you. The account data may be processed for the purposes of operating our website, providing our services, ensuring the security of our website and services, maintaining back-ups of our databases and communicating with you. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business.

2.3 We may process your personal data that are provided in the course of the use of our services (“service data”). The service data may include your IP address and account email address. The service data may be processed for the purposes of operating our website, providing our services, ensuring the security of our website and services, maintaining back-ups of our databases and communicating with you. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business.

2.4 We may process information relating to transactions, including purchases of goods and services, that you enter into with us and/or through our website (“transaction data”). The transaction data may include your contact details, your card details and the transaction details. The transaction data may be processed for the purpose of supplying the purchased goods and services and keeping proper records of those transactions. The legal basis for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract and our legitimate interests, namely our interest in the proper administration of our website and business.

2.5 We may process information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters (“notification data”). The notification data may be processed for the purposes of sending you the relevant notifications and/or newsletters. The legal basis for this processing is consent.

2.6 We may process information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us (“correspondence data”). The correspondence data may include the communication content and metadata associated with the communication. Our website will generate the metadata associated with communications made using the website contact forms. The correspondence data may be processed for the purposes of communicating with you and record-keeping. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business and communications with users.

2.7 We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the protection and assertion of our legal rights, your legal rights and the legal rights of others.

2.8 We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, or obtaining professional advice. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper protection of our business against risks.

2.9 In addition to the specific purposes for which we may process your personal data set out in this Section 2, we may also process any of your personal data where such processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

2.10 Please do not supply any other person’s personal data to us, unless we prompt you to do so.

#### 3\. Providing your personal data to others

3.1 Financial transactions relating to our website and services are OR may be handled by our payment services providers, Braintree Payments and PayPal. We will share transaction data with our payment services providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing your payments, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. You can find information about the payment services providers’ privacy policies and practices at <https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>.

3.2 In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data set out in this Section 3, we may disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person. We may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.

#### 4\. Retaining personal data

4.1 Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.

4.2 Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section 6, we may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

#### 5\. Amendments

5.1 We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.

5.2 We may notify you of changes to this policy by email.

#### 6\. Your rights

6.1 You may instruct us to provide, rectify, delete, or limit any personal information we hold about you; subject to verification of your identity. You may do this in the account section of our website.

6.2 We may withhold personal information that you request to the extent permitted by law.

6.3 You may instruct us at any time not to process your personal information for marketing purposes or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes.

#### 7\. About cookies

7.1 A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

7.2 Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.

7.3 Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

#### 8\. Cookies that we use

8.1 We use cookies for the following purposes:  
(a) authentication – we use cookies to identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website. Cookies used for this purpose are Google Analytics, Zaius, Output and Metorik;  
(b) status – we use cookies to help us to determine if you are logged into our website. Cookies used for this purpose are hosted by Output;  
(c) advertising – we use cookies to help us to display advertisements that will be relevant to you. Cookies used for this purpose are Google and Facebook;  
(d) analysis – we use cookies to help us to analyze the use and performance of our website and services. Cookies used for this purpose are Google Analytics, Zaius, and Metorik.

#### 9\. Cookies used by our service providers

9.1 Our service providers use cookies and those cookies may be stored on your computer when you visit our website.

9.2 We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google’s privacy policy is available at: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>.

9.3 We use Zaius to manage our email list and to analyze sales. Zaius gathers email addresses and sales information when a purchase is made. The information gathered is used to send marketing email and create reports about our sales data. You may opt-out from any direct marketing from the unsubscribe link within each email. You can view the privacy policy of this service provider at <https://www.zaius.com/privacy-policy/>.

#### 10\. Managing cookies

10.1 Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:  
(a) [Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en);  
(b) [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences);  
(c) [Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411);

10.2 Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.

10.3 If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our website.

#### 11\. Our details

11.1 This website is owned and operated by Output Inc.

11.2 We are registered in United States of America and our registered office is at 1418 N Spring St, Suite 102, Los Angeles, CA 90012.

11.3 Our principal place of business is at 1418 N Spring St, Suite 102, Los Angeles, CA 90012.

11.4 You can contact us using our website contact form, or by calling (818) 672-6902

#### 12\. Data protection officer

12.1 Our data protection officer can be reached at [dpo@output.com](mailto:dpo@output.com)

### Want free loops? Plus exclusive offers, production tips, and new product information?

###
